Finding aid for the Xavier University Alumni Association records
Xavier University Archives and Special Collections
- Events and Activities, 1889-2010
  - Annual Chapter Leader Conference, 1957-1974
    - Annual Chapter Leaders Conference, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 203)
    - Annual Chapter Leaders Conference, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 204)
    - Annual Chapter Leaders Conference, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 205)
    - Annual Chapter Leaders Conference, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 206)
  - Alumni Enrollment Ambassadors Program, 2009
    - Alumni Enrollment Ambassadors Program, 2009 (Box 11, Folder 207)
      Copies of booklets (x2) produced to send to individual alumni and chapter presidents assisting with the recruitment of new students.
- Photographs, 1904-1913
  Photographs of the Class of 1914; photograph of the Class of 1903, plus a sheet music cover of a song, " Dark Doin's, dedicated to the class.
  - Photographs, 1904-1913 (Box 11, Folder 208)
- Miscellaneous, 1909-1946; undated
  Notes for a speech by Father Nieporte (undated); "novelty" certificate awarded to Francis A. Gauche (1909); extract from "The Cincinnati Enquirer" reporting a service hald to honor Xavier's war dead (3 Jun 1946)
  - Miscellaneous, 1909-1946; undated (Box 11, Folder 209)
- Affiliations, 1902-1956; undated
  Mainly papers, correspondence and publicity materials relating to the National Catholic Alumni Federation and the Alumni Association's involvement.
  - National Catholic Alumni Federation, 1925-1942; undated
    Papers, correspondence and publicity materials relating to the NCAF and Alumni Association's involvement.
    - National Catholic Alumni Federation, 1925-1932 (Box 11, Folder 210)
    - National Catholic Alumni Federation, 1933 (Box 11, Folder 211)
    - National Catholic Alumni Federation, 1934-1935 (Box 12, Folder 212)
    - National Catholic Alumni Federation, 1936-1939 (Box 12, Folder 213)
    - National Catholic Alumni Federation, 1940-1942; undated (Box 12, Folder 214)
    - National Catholic Alumni Federation: Bulletins, 1935-1937 (Box 12, Folder 215)
  - Miscellaneous, 1902-1956; undated
    - Affiliations: Miscellaneous, 1902-1956; undated (Box 12, Folder 216)
      Jesuit Alumni Association booklet (x2), including the constitution and a brief history of the Association (1902); "Constitution and By-laws of the Federation of Alumni Associations of Jesuit Colleges in the United States" (undated); program for the "Silver Jubilee and Federation Exercises"of the Federation of Alumni Associations of Jesuit Colleges in the United States (1906); papers relating to the Jesuit Educational Association (1955-1956).
- Alumnae Association records, 1926-1974
  - Administration, 1926-1974; undated
    - Alumnae: Constitution and By-Laws, 1926-1963 (Box 12, Folder 217)
      Copies of the Association constitution and by-laws, plus correspondence and drafts relating to revisions. Also, leaflets outlining the structure and function of the Association.
    - Board of Governors: Membership Lists, 1935-1974; undated (Box 12, Folder 218)
      Lists of officers of the Alumnae Association.
    - Alumni Association: Board Minutes, 1952-1973 (Box 12, Folder 219)
      Minutes and papers relating to meetings of the Alumnae Association Board of Governors.
    - Alumnae: Finances, 1931-1963 (Box 12, Folder 220)
      Copies of requisition forms for supplies, catering, printing, etc.
    - Alumnae: Living Endowment Fund, 1963-1969 (Box 12, Folder 221)
      Publicity material, honor rolls, correspondence and financial reports relating to the annual Living Endowment Fund appeal.
    - Alumnae: Correspondence, 1941-1969 (Box 12, Folder 222)
      Miscellaneous correspondence concerning the Alumnae Association, much of it received by Father William A. Dowd.
  - Membership, 1932-1961; undated
    - Alumnae: Alumnae Listings, 1932-1961; undated (Box 12, Folder 223)
      Lists of members of the Association, plus a small ledger containing a record of dues paid.
  - Alumni Relations, 1942-1973
    Issues of Alumnae Notes for various years.
    - Alumnae: Annual Bulletin, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 224)
    - Alumnae: Annual Bulletin, 1957-1958 (Box 13, Folder 225)
    - Alumnae: Annual Bulletin, 1959-1960 (Box 13, Folder 226)
    - Alumnae: Annual Bulletin, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 227)
    - Alumnae: Annual Bulletin, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 228)
    - Alumnae: Annual Bulletin, 1963-1964 (Box 13, Folder 229)
    - Alumnae: Annual Bulletin, 1965-1966 (Box 13, Folder 230)
    - Alumnae: Annual Bulletin, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 231)
    - Alumnae: Annual Bulletin, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 232)
    - Alumnae: Annual Bulletin, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 233)
    - Alumnae: Annual Bulletin, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 234)
    - Alumnae: Annual Bulletin, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 235)
    - Alumnae: Annual Bulletin, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 236)
    - Alumnae: Annual Bulletin, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 237)
  - Alumnae Relations: Events and Activities, 1942-1970
    - Alumnae: Events and Activities, 1942-1970 (Box 13, Folder 238)
      Newsletters, correspondence, invitations, flyers, reports, newspaper clippings and other papers relating to events and activities staged by the Alumnae Association.
  - Affiliations, 1961-1989
    - Alumnae: International Federation of Catholic Alumnae, 1962-1969 (Box 13, Folder 239)
      Information relating to the IFCA, including an outline of its history, purpose and organization (1962), copies of the IFCA Bulletin (Mar 1963, Sept 1969), and a directory of members (1961-1964).
- Oversized Materials and Volumes, 1904-1980
  - Administration, 1903-1919
    - Alumni Association Receipts, 1903-1909; Fragile volume. (Box 14, Folder 241)
      A volume of receipts for goods and services.
    - Alumni Association Meeting Minutes, 1904-1919; Fragile volume. (Box 14, Folder 242)
      Minutes and papers of the committees of the Alumni Association, including the Board of Governors.
  - Events and Activities, 1980
    - Reunions: Class of 1970 Proclamation, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 243)
      Class of 1970 proclamation from the Mayor of Cincinnati's office, J. Kenneth Blackwell (1970 alum), declaring October 24 and 25, 1980 to be Xavier Class of 1970 Homecoming Days.